<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>science on akash stephen</title>
    <link>https://akashstephen.github.io/tags/science/</link>
    <description>Recent content in science on akash stephen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2022</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 20:50:40 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://akashstephen.github.io/tags/science/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>JWST releasing its first image!</title>
      <link>https://akashstephen.github.io/blog/jwstpics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 20:50:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akashstephen.github.io/blog/jwstpics/</guid>
      <description>NASA just announced that the James Webb Space Telescope&amp;rsquo;s first images are coming out on July 12 2022! This is the most exciting thing this month. The images from this giant telescope is going to be the most spectacular view of our universe!
#UnfoldTheUniverse</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Growing plants in Lunar soil!</title>
      <link>https://akashstephen.github.io/blog/blog-post4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 15:04:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akashstephen.github.io/blog/blog-post4/</guid>
      <description>Scientists at NASA grew Arabidopsis (which is the most studied plant of all time) in Lunar Soil!!! Samples of lunar soil were brought back by the Apollo Missions (11,12,and 17). They say that the plants sprouted in just two days!
Interestingly there were differences in the growth among the different samples. Most notably the Apollo 11 mission samples were under a lot of stress (but still managed to sprout!).
 credits : UF/IFAS photo by Tyler Jones</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life found on a 830 million year old rock?</title>
      <link>https://akashstephen.github.io/blog/blog-post2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 15:34:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://akashstephen.github.io/blog/blog-post2/</guid>
      <description>I just saw this video about finding life embedded inside rock salt in Australia thats 830 million years old. Crazy stuff. Apparently the water and the minerals kept these prokaryotes in a habitable ecosystem. We dont really know if they are alive tho, but it is fascinating to realise that life existed in such salty and harsh environments. Can&amp;rsquo;t wait for the day we find live on another planet.
video link : https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
